<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Davenport Lab</title>
    <link>https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Davenport Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Openings</title>
      <link>https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/openings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/openings/</guid>
      <description>The lab is expanding! We are seeking undergraduate researchers, graduate students, and postdocs/research associates.
Undergraduate Researchers Undergraduates interested in gaining research experience examining questions related to host-microbe interactions should reach out to Emily to see whether there are opennings in the lab. Projects in the lab involve bench lab work (wet), computational research (dry), or a combination of both. Prospective researchers should be willing to make a time commitment of at least 8 hours per week to their research during fall and spring semesters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description>Laboratory:
Pennsylvania State University
Department of Biology
Wartik Laboratory - Room 302
University Park, PA 16802</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macrobes</title>
      <link>https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/people/</guid>
      <description>We are! The Macrobe + microbe interaction lab in the Department of Biology at the Pennsylvania State University. We use a combination of wet lab and computational approaches to understand what determines microbiome composition within a host, and how the relationship between the host and the microbiome affects host health and evolution.
Emily Davenport
Assistant Professor
Department of Biology
Huck Institutes of the Life Sciences and Institute for Computational and Data Sciences</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/publications/</guid>
      <description>See my google scholar profile for an up-to-date list.
* denotes equal contribution
underlined denotes Davenport lab member
2021  Jeganathan NA, Davenport ER, Yochum GS, and Koltun WA. The microbiome in diverticulitis. Current Opinion in Physiology. 2021;22 Amato KR, Arrieta M, Azad MB, Bailey MT, Broussard JL, Bruggeling CE, Claud EC, Costello EK, Davenport ER, Dutilh BE, Swain Ewald HA, Ewald P, Hanlon EC, Julion W, Keshavarzian A, Maurice CF, Miller GE, Preidis GA, Segurel L, Singer B, Subramanian S, Zhao L, and Kuzawa CW.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>