<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Davenport Lab</title>
    <link>http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Davenport Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Openings</title>
      <link>http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/openings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/openings/</guid>
      <description>The lab is expanding! We are currently seeking undergraduate researchers, graduate students, and postdocs/research associates:
Undergraduate Researchers The lab is seeking undergraduates interested in gaining research experience examining questions related to host-microbe interactions. Projects in the lab involve bench lab work (wet), computational research (dry), or a combination of both. Prospective researchers should be willing to make a time commitment of at least 8 hours per week to their research during the semesters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description>Laboratory:
Pennsylvania State University
Department of Biology
Wartik Laboratory - Room 302
University Park, PA 16802</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Macrobes</title>
      <link>http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/people/</guid>
      <description>We are! The Macrobe + microbe interaction lab in the Department of Biology at the Pennsylvania State University. We use a combination of wet lab and computational approaches to understand what determines microbiome composition within a host, and how the relationship between the host and the microbiome affects host health and evolution.
Emily Davenport
Assistant Professor
Department of Biology
Huck Institutes of the Life Sciences and Institute for CyberScience</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://davenport-lab.github.io/pages/publications/</guid>
      <description>See my google scholar profile for an up-to-date list.
* denotes equal contribution
2019  Gong X, Davenport ER, Wang D, Clark AG. Lack of spatial and temporal genetic structure of Anguilla japonica populations. Conservation Genetics. 2019 Kachoo P*, Eraso JM*, Beres SB, Olsen RJ, Zhu L, Nasser W, Bernard PE, Cantu CC., Ojeda Saavedtra M, José Arredondo M, Strope B, Do H, Kumaraswami M, Vuopio J, Gröndahl-Yli-Hannuksela K, Kristinsson KG, Gottfredsson M, Pesonen M, Pensar J, Davenport ER, Clark AG, Corander J, Caugant DA, Gaini S, Magnusses MD, Porter AR, DeLeoFR, and Musser JM.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>